Coordonnées

huu1511@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ nguyenhauhuu (LinkedIn)

Principales compétences

Project Planning
Project Management
Renewable Energy

Nguyen Hau Huu, PMP®

Project Manager at BIM/AC ENERGY

District de Thủ Đức, Ho Chi Minh-Ville, Việt Nam

Résumé

I have worked for more than 13 years in Civil Construction and now I work as Project Manager for Wind Power Plant Project. With many years of experience working in multinational projects such as thermal power plant, refinery plant, solar farm and wind farm. I have accumulated many experiences in project management such as:

- Leading and managing construction projects and resolving site issues promptly.
- Proposing suitable construction methods to ensure quality
- Managing all project documentation through close-out.
- Having a good relationship/interface with All Parties.
- Maintaining safe work environments.

Expérience

BIM/AC ENERGY

Project Manager août 2020 - Present (4 ans 8 mois)

Ninh Thuan, Vietnam

- Organizing the project management team.
- Coordinating with related departments in HQ to manage the contract of the project.
- Lead and manage the project team including the owner's engineer, contractors, and internal project members.
- Supervise the construction process in accordance with company policy about quality, volume, progress, labor safety, environmental sanitation of project.
- Appraisal of project dossiers, technical design, construction supervision.
- Working with the authorities on the legal procedures of the project.

- Advising the board of management of the company to choose the plan to organize the project management and implementation of the project.
- Timely handling of all problems, ensuring the implementation plan of the project.

Sunseap Energy Project Director juillet 2019 - août 2020 (1 an 2 mois)

Vietnam

- Manage all aspects of subcontract administration for the project, from bidding
 to prequalified bidders, negotiation/execution of subcontracts, work orders,
 submitting notices and change orders and closing out contracts after the
 substantial completion of projects.
- Oversee and manage the various general conditions services required for EPC projects.
- Report the contract status and schedule with project teams and management weekly
- Support in the assembly and issuance of Subcontracts, Purchase Orders, Change Orders and other contracts management documents.
- Determine project management, technical services and external resources required for the project on an individual and team basis.
- Develop, manage and maintain effective relationships with key internal and external stakeholders, building networks and leveraging relationships to maximize opportunities.
- Lead and manage the project team including owner's engineer, contractors, and internal project members.

TTC Group

1 an 3 mois

Project Manager novembre 2018 - juillet 2019 (9 mois)

Tây Ninh Province

- Manage project permitting including interactions with national, provincial, and local government entities; industry groups; and local stakeholders.
- Collaborate with technical, legal, and financial resources to support the project development process.
- Ensure that the EPC Contractor meet the contractual conditions of performance as per the scope of work and timeline and the project is commissioned within the contractual COD date.

Deputy Project Manager mai 2018 - novembre 2018 (7 mois)

Ho Chi Minh

- Manage project permitting including interactions with national, provincial, and local government entities; industry groups; and local stakeholders.
- Collaborate with technical, legal, and financial resources to support the project development process.
- Ensure that the EPC Contractor meet the contractual conditions of performance as per the scope of work and timeline and the project are commissioned within the contractual COD date.
- Check designs for site layout, including access roads, PV module layout, and execute the civil infrastructure accordingly
- Conduct construction monitoring inspections of projects to verify compliance with: Construction plans and specifications & Applicable code requirements and standards and good construction practice.
- Review the work progress on daily basis and publish progress reports as per the project reporting requirements and publish the required routine reports on time;
- Track, manage and process all variations in accordance with company policy and within budgetary constraints.
- Ensure safety standards of the site are adhered to by the civil works subcontractors when work is underway and regulations relating to health, safety and the environment (HSE) are adhered to;

PTSC

6 ans 7 mois

Deputy Engineer Manager avril 2016 - mai 2018 (2 ans 2 mois) Soc Trang

Project: Long Phu 1 Thermal Power Plant

Duties:

- Be responsible to the Engineering Manager for any civil design.
- To coordinate with construction team and design team to involve and resolve which issue related with engineering work.
- To coordinate with document controller team on design deliverables transaction to ensure smooth flow of documents and timely design submissions as well as expedite PM/Vendor for submission on time, connect Owner to review/comment/approve progress and sent related document design to SUB also.

- Direct, urge and supervise the civil design and implementation of construction drawings for the project.
- Assignment of work to the Organization, successful organization of quality, progress and efficiency. Checking, casting, dealing with problems during the implementation of work for employees.
- Monitor and collect data base of design, standard application.
- Manage the interfaces between disciplines, clients and companies relating to civil engineering.
- Take part in Design Review Meeting, Monthly Progress Meeting, and Weekly Consortium Meeting.

Civil Superintendent

juillet 2014 - avril 2016 (1 an 10 mois)

Nghi Son, Thanh Hoa

Project: Nghi Son Refinery (NSRP)

Duties:

- Assist in the development and maintenance of preconstruction, construction, and closeout execution plans
- Assist in reviewing project drawings and specifications to gain a full understanding of project scope, client goals and expectations, and resource requirements for each phase of the project
- Identify construction approaches and risks to ensure efficiency and mitigate exposure.
- Prepare method statement of deep excavation with sheet piling protection;
 execution plan.
- Assist in soliciting and coordinating subcontractor and supplier bids for labor, material and equipment
- Assist in the development and maintenance of project schedules, durations, and sequencing logic
- Oversee the activities and performance of subcontractors and suppliers to ensure compliance with quality requirements
- Monitor project progress to ensure compliance with financial, operational, and/or scheduling requirements
- Resolve worksite issues quickly and effectively in order to keep work progress on track
- Gather information, develop solutions, and adjust to necessary changes in work sequences
- Assist in evaluating the legitimacy of subcontractor and supplier change requests in terms of contractual requirements and validity of cost estimates

- Maintain a safe, secure, and healthy work environment by following and enforcing standards and procedures;
- Provide a daily report of site conditions including weather, work scope, force levels, and safety issues
- Supervise completion of punch-lists, close-out documentation, and demobilize the job site at the completion of a project

Civil team leader

novembre 2011 - juillet 2014 (2 ans 9 mois)

Soc Trang

Project: Long Phu 1 Thermal Power Plant

Duties:

- Site Supervisor for soil improvement work (PVD+Vacum method).
- Site Supervisor for soil investigation after soil improvement work.
- Supervisor for laboratory testing
- Prepare acceptance document.
- Control and chase up Subcontractor to follow the project schedule.
- · Interface with clients and Consultant.
- Review and comment method statement and execution plan from Subcontractors.
- Prepare the daily report, weekly report and monthly report for site activity.
- Submit all site report to Owner and PMC;
- · Make EPC document proposal;
- Material take off for cost estimate of EPC package;
- Prepare as built document for soil improvement work.

TECHNICAL WORLD LTD

Site Manager

avril 2010 - novembre 2011 (1 an 8 mois)

Ho Chi Minh City

Duties:

- Manage geotechnical and geological analyses, manage staff, conduct research, perform preliminary geological report, geotechnical and geological report;
- Review testing results and develop design recommendations.
- Interface with clients, Supervisor teams and Consultant.
- Make decisions on Method Statement and Execution Plan
- Cooperate with support staff, laboratory staff and document production staff for the report of soil investigation result.
- Develop, manage and perform field work for geotechnical and geological studies in accordance with clients.

- Prepare documents detailing analysis and recommendations.
- Manage budgets, write and edit reports and proposals to Manager Project:
- Formosa Ha Tinh integrated steel mill;
- Trung Luong My Thuan Expressway;
- · Vietnam Financial Centre;
- · Happy Land;
- STT Thu Tam Building;
- Nguyen Kim Apartment;
- 91 Highway;
- 62 Highway;

Nam Bo Geology Company Chief Technical Officer mai 2007 - mars 2010 (2 ans 11 mois) Ho Chi Minh City

Duties:

- · Site Supervisor for soil investigation.
- Make a daily report to Owner.
- Make acceptance documents, QC document.
- Establish geology survey report;
- Make the geology map; hydrological geology map, mineral resources map, the topographic map;
- Prepare bidder document.
- Prepare mineral resources exploitation;
- Prepare exploration projects, inventory planning, establishment of mining projects, construction of mining facilities, mining license
- Prepare report for material exploration of backfill for encroach marine project in Kien Giang Province

Projects:

- Kumho Golf site, District 9, HCM City;
- Sacombank Branches in South provinces;
- Some mineral exploration project such as: Peat, Clay, Clay for Cement,
 Sand, Building stone, Kaolin in South Provinces;
- Establish mineral resources planning in Ben Tre, Kien Giang, Dong Thap province:
- A.C.M marine encroachment in Ha Tien (ACM Company);
- Hai Au marine encroachment in Rach Gia (ITA group);
- Toan Thanh Tam tuynel brick factory in Ha Tien (Toan Thinh Phat group);
- Kaolin exploitation in Minh Long, Binh Phuoc (BIMICO);

• Illuminate exploitation in Binh Thuan (Hop Long group).

Formation

Ho Chi Minh University of Technology

Master's degree, Geotechnical Engineering · (2007 - 2009)

Ho Chi Minh University of Technology
Bachelor's degree, Geochemistry and Petrology · (2002 - 2007)